realtrafficsource.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy | RealTrafficSource.com

[](https://i1.wp.com/realtrafficsource.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/08/privacy.png)We at [Real Traffic Source](http://realtrafficsource.com/) respect and are committed to protecting our clients’ privacy. With this intention we have adopted our Privacy Policy.

Under no circumstances will we sell your personal information with any person or organization. We will not sell or otherwise disclose, except as required by law, your email address or any other information we collect as a result of your visit to our site or your becoming a customer/reseller. Real Traffic Source does not engage in sending unsolicited email, and we will not knowingly participate in business with anyone who does. We may send out marketing materials sent out directly by Real Traffic Source about special advertising offers.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Cookies

The Real Traffic Source site uses cookies whose purpose is to facilitate navigation on the site, to execute the service provided by Real Traffic Source, to measure the site’s audience, or to allow pages on the site to be shared.

#### Types of cookies used

##### The cookies necessary for navigation on the site

These cookies are necessary for the functioning of the Real Traffic Source site. They allow the main features of the site to be used.

Without these cookies, Users cannot use the site normally.

##### Functional cookies

These cookies make it possible to personalise the User experience.

##### Analytical cookies

These cookies make it possible to examine the use and the performance of the site and to improve its operation by carrying out analyses of visits to the informational pages by monitoring the open rates, the click rates, and the bounce rates at the individual level.

##### Sharing button cookies

These social cookies allow users to share pages and content on third-party social networks via social sharing buttons.
